Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Communist and Socialist Serials TAM.747
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: American Publications, 1881-2010; 68.4 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 102 flat boxes
  - Don't Strangle the Party: Three Letters and a Talk: Fourth Internationalist Tendency, New York, NY, 1986; cuid11726 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Information Letter: Fourth Internationalist Tendency, Brooklyn, NY, 1984-1985; cuid11727 (Box 159, Folder 1-2, Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Internal Information Bulletin: Fourth Internationalist Tendency, Brooklyn, NY, 1984-1985; cuid11728 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - A Year of Decision for US Labor: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1985; cuid11729 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - American Elections and the Issues Facing Working People: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1988; cuid11730 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Malcolm X: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1990; cuid11731 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Organizing for Socialism: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1991; cuid11732 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Permanent Revolution in Nicaragua: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1984; cuid11733 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Permanent Revolution, Combined Revolution, adn Black Liberation in the United States: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1989; cuid11734 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Revolutionary Traditions of American Trotskyism: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1988; cuid11735 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - The Cuban Revolution, the Castroist Current, and the Fourth International: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1981; cuid11736 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - The Struggle to Build a Revolutionary Party: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1990; cuid11737 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - The Trenton Siege by the Army of Occupation: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1986; cuid11738 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Upheaval in China: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1989; cuid11739 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Vanguard Parties: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1991; cuid11740 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Where is the Soviet Union Heading: Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1991; cuid11741 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Free Association Newsletter: Free Association, New York, NY, 1976; cuid11742 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Daily Worker: Freedom of the Press Co., New York, NY, 1945 (Box 205, Folder 3, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 14)
  - Freedom Socialist: Freedom Socialist Party, Seattle, WA, 1976-2010; cuid11743 (Box 91, Folder 2-8, Box 92, Folder 1-3, Box 122, Folder 26)
  - FSP Pre-Convention Discussion Bulletin: Freedom Socialist Party, Seattle, WA, 1982; cuid11744 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Introducing the Freedom Socialist Party: Freedom Socialist Party, Seattle, WA, 1967; cuid11745 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - The Chicano Struggle: a racial or a national movement?: Freedom Socialist Party, Seattle, WA, 1983-1989; cuid13384 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Due to the fragile condition of this material, access may be supervised or restricted.
  - Friday: Friday, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1940-1941; cuid11746 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Groundwork: From the Ground Up, Detroit, MI, 1973; cuid11747 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Internationale Arbeiter Front Gegen Den Krieg: Front Ouvrier International Contre La Guerre, 1940; cuid11748 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Perestroika: Frontline, Oakland, CA, 1988; cuid11749 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Set on Freedom: Ft. Greene Club of the Communist Party, Brooklyn, NY, 1985; cuid11750 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Gay Socialist Newsletter: Gay Socialist Action Project of NYC, New York, NY, 1977; cuid11751 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - White Power: George Lincoln Rockwell Party Incorporated, Arlington, VA, 1974; cuid11752 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - W.O.K.S.: gesellschaft fur kulturelle verbindung der sowjetunion mit dem auslande, 1933; cuid11753 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Forward: Getting Together Publications, Oakland, CA, 1986-1989; cuid11754 (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
  - Normalization of US-China Relations and Deng Xiaoing's US Visit: A Victory for Socialism: Getting Together Publications, San Francisco, CA, 1978; cuid11755 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Statements on the Founding of the League of Revolutionary Struggle: Getting Together Publications, United States, 1978; cuid11756 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Special Discussion Bulletin on Draft Constitution and Preamble: GF Communism - US, San Francisco, CA, 1947; cuid11757 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Through Soviet Eyes: Greater Boston Committee, American-Soviet Friendship, Inc., Boston, MA, 1987; cuid11758 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Voice of the Worker: Greek Socialist Union, New York, New York, 1918-1923; cuid13355 (Box 197, Folder 2-3)
  - Radical Periodicals in the United States, 1890-1960: Modern Socialism: Greenwood Reprint Corporation, New York, NY, 1968; cuid11759 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Radical Periodicals in the United States, 1890-1960: World Survey: Greenwood Reprint Corporation, New York, NY, 1968; cuid11760 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin Interieur du Groupe Bolchevik-Leniniste: Groupe Bolchevik-Leniniste, 1934-1936; cuid11761 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Malcolm X on Organization: Grove Press/ Independent publisher copying from Grove Press, New York, NY, 1965; cuid11762 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - For the Reforging of the Fourth International: Gruppe IV. Internationale, Berlin, Germany, circa 1990s; cuid11763 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Bandiera Rossa: Gruppi Comunisti Revoluzionari Sezione Italiana della IV Internazionale, NY, 1967-1969; cuid11764 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Man Bites Dog: Report of an unusual hearing before the McCarran Committee: Guardian Pamphlets/National Guardian, New York, NY, 1952; cuid11765 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Guardian Sustainer: Guardian Sustainer/ Guardian Sustainer Program, New York, NY, 1976, 1989; cuid11766 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Haldeman-Julius Quarterly: Haldeman-Julius Company, Girard, KS, 1928; cuid11767 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Against Reagan Racism: Enemy of the American People: Hall-Davis Campaign '84, New York, NY, 1984; cuid11768 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Which Path--Cowardice or the Teaching of Mao Tse-Tung: Hammer & Steel, Boston, MA, 1963; cuid11769 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Brothers and Sisters of Harlem! (construction project flyer): Harlem Section, Communist Party of New York State, New York, NY, circa 1990s; cuid11770 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Harvard Socialist: Harvard-Radcliffe Young People's Socialist League, cambridge, MA, 1969; cuid11771 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - ISO Bulletin: Hera Press, Cleveland, OH, 1979; cuid11772 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - American Imperialism and White Chauvinism: Herbert Aptheker, 1949, 1950; cuid11773 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Thesis and Resolutions for the Seventh National Convention of the Communist Party USA: Historical Documentation Committee: Asia Books & Periodicals, Arlington, VA, 1930; cuid11774 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Marxist: Homogeneous Party of the Workinh Class in the U.S.A., New York, Ny, 1978-1980, 1983-1984, 1988; cuid11775 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Me and My Captain: (Chain Gang): Negro Songs of Protest: Hours Press, New York, NY, 1939; cuid11776 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Proposals of the Eighth National Congress of the Communist Party of China for the Second Five-Year Plan for Development of the National Economy: Hsinhua News Agency, 1962; cuid11777 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Russia: Perspectives on the Revolution/Early Soviet Literature: Hyperion Press, Westport, CT, circa 1960s; cuid11778 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Chicago, City of Haymarket, Welcomes the 21st National Convention CPUSA: Illinois-Iowa District, CPUSA/New Outlook Publishers, Chicago, IL/New York, NY, 1975; cuid11779 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Imported Publications Catalog: Imported Publications, Inc., Chicago, IL, 1988; cuid11780 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - La Lettre d'Informations ouvrieres: Imprimerie IO, Paris, 1979; cuid11781 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - I.S. Independent Socialist: A Revolutionary Socialist Monthly: Indenpendent Socialist Clubs of America, Berkeley, CA, 1969; cuid11782 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Souvenir of the Ninetheenth Annual Conference of the Independent Labor Party: Independent Labour Party, Birmingham, AL, 1911; cuid11783 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - IS Fund Drive Bulletin: Independent Socialist, Highland Park, MI, 1972; cuid11784 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Peace and Freedom Party and the McCarthy Dissidents: Independent Socialist Club, circa 1960s; cuid11785 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Crisis in the Schools: Independent Socialist Clubs of America, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11786 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Forum: Discussion and Information Bulletin of the Independent Socialist League: Independent Socialist League, Oakland, CA, 1952; cuid11787 (Box 141, Folder 4, Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Thieu's Political Prisoners (Indochina Chronicle?): Indochina Resource Center, Washington, DC, 1972; cuid11788 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Viet-Nam: What Kind of Peace?: Documents and Analysis of the 1973 Paris Agreement on Viet-Nam: Indochina Resource Center, Washington, DC, cuid11789 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Reform or Revolution: Industrial Union Party, New York, NY, 1934; cuid11790 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - The Soviet Position on Prohibition of Atomic Weapons and International Control of Atomic Energy: Information Bulletin of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, Washington, DC, 1949; cuid11791 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Delaware Valley democratic Left: Institute for Democratic Socialism, Philadelphia, PA, 1995-1996; cuid11792 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Third World Socialists: Institute for Democratic Socialism, New York, NY, circa 1980s; cuid11793 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Public Policy Papers: Institute for East-West Security Studies, New York, NY, 1990; cuid11794 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Catalyst: A Socialist Journal of the Social Services: Institute for Social Service Alternatives, Inc., New York, NY, 1978, 1980-1981; cuid11795 (Box 141, Folder 11, Box Shared Tamiment 183, Folder 3)
  - Eighties: Institute for the Study of Creative Policy Alternatives, Inc., Brooklyn, NY, 1983-1985; cuid11796 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - World Capitalist Crisis and the Rise of the Right: Institute for the Study of Labor and Economic Crisis/ Synthesis Publications, San Diego, CA, 1982; cuid11797 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Bulletin: Institute for the Study of the USSR, 1957; cuid11798 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Allegeny Socialist: Institute of Democratic Socialism, 1991-1993; cuid11799 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Insurgent Sociologist: Insurgent Socialist, St. Louis, MO, 1970; cuid11800 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter: Inter-Regional Committee of the Committees of Correspondence, St. Paul, MN, 1985; cuid13379 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - Annual Statement of the Intercollegiate Socialist Society: Intercollegiate Socialist Society, New York, NY, 1911; cuid11801 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin of the Intercollegiate Socialist Society: Intercollegiate Socialist Society, New York, NY, 1910, 1912; cuid11802 (Box 141, Folder 16, Box 122, Folder 20)
  - 1979 World Congress of the Fourth International: Intercontinental Press, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Internationl Discussion Bulletin: Interim International Secretariat, New York, NY, 1976; cuid11803 (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - Seize the Times: Internal Newsletter of the Attica Brigade, Staten Island, NY, 1974; cuid11804 (Box 141, Folder 18, Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Together Against Imperialism, For Peace, Democracy, Freedom and Socialism: International Affairs Department, Central Committee, CPUSA, New York, NY, 1979; cuid11805 (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - Challenge: International Arts & Sciences Press, Inc., White Plains, NY, 1975; cuid11806 (Box 141, Folder 20)
  - International Review: International Associates, New York, NY, 1937-1938; cuid11807 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - International Bulletin: International bureau of revolutionary youth organizations, New York, NY, 1934-1935; cuid11808 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Internationalism/WR Pamphlet: International Communist Current, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid11809 (Box 65, Folder 5, Box 66, Folder 1-3)
  - Forward for the Reconstruction: International Executive Committee of the international league for the reconstruction of the fourth international, 1988; cuid11810 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Annual Bazaar: International Labor Defense, New York, NY, 1933-1934; cuid11811 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Educational Bulletin: International Labor Defense, circa 1940s; cuid11812 (Box 142, Folder 5, Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Equal Justice' Year Book of the Fight for Democratic Rights 1936-37: International Labor Defense, New York, NY, 1937; cuid11813 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - International Labor Defense Legislative Service: International Labor Defense, New York, NY, 1945-1946; cuid11814 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Service: International Labor Defense, New York, NY, 1941; cuid11815 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Marxism and the Mass Media: towards a basic bibliography: International Mass Media Research Center/ I.G. Editions, New York, NY, 1974, 1976; cuid11816 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Forward: A Journal of Marxist Theory: International Party of Revolutionary Workers (Fourth International)/ Revolutionary Workers Group, 1974; cuid11817 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Book Newsletter: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1973, 1980, 1981; cuid11818 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Book Newsletter & Full Catalog: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1991-1992, 1996; cuid11819 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Chief Stages in History of C.P.S.U.: International Publishers, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid11820 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Economic Problems of Socialism in the USSR: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1952; cuid11821 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Foundations of Leninism: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1939; cuid11822 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - France Faces Her Destiny: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1946; cuid11823 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Little Lenin Library: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1934; cuid11824 (Box 142, Folder 19, Box 228, Folder 8)
  - Little Lenin Library - Volume 15 - Imperialism - The Highest Stage of Capitalism: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1939; cuid11825 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Little Lenin Library: Imperialism the Highest Stage of Capitalism: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1933; cuid11826 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Little Lenin Library: Marxism and Revisionism: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1946; cuid11827 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Manifesto of the Communist Party: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1983; cuid11828 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Marx and Science: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1952; cuid11829 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Political Economy in the Soviet Union: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1944; cuid11830 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Reminiscences of Lenin: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1934; cuid11831 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Woman Question: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1951; cuid11832 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - XVII Congress CPSU: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1934; cuid11833 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Women and Society: International Publishers Co. Inc., New York, NY, 1938; cuid11834 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Engels on Capital: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1937; cuid11835 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Lenin Speaks to the Youth: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1936; cuid11836 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Marxism and Poetry: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1946; cuid11837 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Materialist Conception of History: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1940; cuid11838 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Part Played by Labor in the Transition from Ape to Man: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1950; cuid11839 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Value, Price and Profit: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1935; cuid11840 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Wage-Labour and Capital: International Publishers Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1933; cuid11841 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Marxist Study Courses: International Publishers/ The Garden City Press, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid11842 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Imperialism: The Highest Stage of Capialism: International Publishing Company, New York, NY, 1933; cuid11843 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - International Review of Contemporary Thought & Action: International Review, New York, NY, 1936; cuid11844 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - State and the Socialist Revolution: International Review, New York, NY, 1938; cuid11845 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Forum: International Socialist Clubs of America, 1970; cuid11846 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Workers' Organizer: International Socialist League, 1988; cuid11847 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Red Rose: International Socialist Organization, Seattle, WA, 1976; cuid11848 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Strike at UC: International Socialist Publication, Berkeley, CA, 1972; cuid11849 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Chile: The Road to Disaster: International Socialist Publishing Company, Highland Park, MI, 1973; cuid11850 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - International Socialists - pamphlets: International Socialists, New York, NY, 1970, 1974, 1978; cuid11851 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Information Bulletin: International Socialists, Chicago, IL, 1973; cuid11852 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - International Socialist Discussion Pamphlet: International Socialists, Los Angeles, CA, 1974; cuid11853 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - National Secretary's Report: International Socialists, 1973; cuid11854 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Women in the Chinese Revolution: International Socialists, New York, NY, 1927; cuid11855 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Bulletin of the International Socialists: International Socialists League, New York, NY, 1965-1969; cuid11856 (Box 140, Folder 1-6)
  - Solidaridad: International Workers of the World, 2007; cuid11857 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Struggle: International Workers Party, New York, NY, 1976; cuid11858 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Internationalism: Political Perspective: Internationalism, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid11859 (Box 56, Folder 4, Box 65)
  - Decadence of Capitalism: Internationalism/World Revolution, New York, NY/London, England, 1975; cuid11860 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Dossier - Class Struggle and Repression in Vota Redonda, Brazil: Internationalist Group, New York, NY, 1997; cuid11861 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Iskra: Internationalist Workers Party (Fourth International), San Francisco, CA, 1990; cuid11862 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Working Class Opposition: Monthly Newspaper of the Internationalist Workers Party (Fourth International): Internationalist Workers Party (Fourth International), San Francisco, CA, 1984-1990; cuid11863 (Box 117, Folder 2-6)
  - Kaylands Monthly: J.A. Wayland Publisher, Girard, KA, 1908; cuid11864 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Changes in Bourgeois Nationalism (from the Jacobins to the "Munichites"): Jefferson School of Social Science, New York, NY, 1939; cuid11865 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Class Forces in the Development of Free Public Education in the US: Jefferson School of Social Science, New York, NY, 1955; cuid11866 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science: Jefferson School of Social Science, New York, NY, 1947; cuid11867 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Negro People in the United States: Facts for All Americans: Jefferson School of Social Science, New York, NY, 1953; cuid11868 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Notes on the Puerto Rican Question: Jefferson School of Social Science, New York, NY, 1953; cuid11869 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - "An End to the Neglect of the Problems of the Negro Woman!": Jefferson School of Social Science/Political Affairs, New York, NY, 1949; cuid11870 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Le Jeune Leniniste: Jeunesses Leninistes, 1934; cuid11871 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Status of Jews in the Soviet Union: Jewish Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1962; cuid11872 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - The Jewish Socialist: Jewish Socialist Federation of America, Chicago, IL, 1913-1914 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Der Wecker: Jewish Socialist Verband, New York, NY, 1950; cuid11873 (Box 35, Folder 33, Box 39, Folder 1, Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin: John Birch Society, Inc., Belmont, MA, 1963-1964; cuid11874 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - For Revolution: John Day Pamphlets, 1932; cuid11875 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Internal Bulletin of the Johnson Forest Tendency: Johnson Foreign Tendency, 1947; cuid11876 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Novosti: Kathryn W. and Shelby Cullom Davis Center for Russian and Eurasian Studies, Cambridge, MA, 2004; cuid11877 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter of the Kathryn W. and Shelby Cullom Davis Center for Russian Studies: Kathryn W. and Shelby Cullom Davis Center for Russian Studies, Cambridge, MA, 1998-1999, 2001; cuid11878 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Report: Kennan Institute, Washington, DC, 1997-1998, 2000-2009; cuid11879 (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
  - New Road: Kollektiv, New York, NY, 1941-1944; cuid11880 (Box 39, Folder 9-10)
  - Claridad Proletaria: La Liga Comunista de America, 1933; cuid11881 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - How to Write for Labor Action - Style Sheet: Labor Action, circa 1950s; cuid11882 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Worker: Labor Party League, Montclair, CA, 1975-1976; cuid11883 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Labor Power: Labor Power, New York, NY, 1939-1940; cuid11884 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - International Workers Bulletin: Labor Publications, Southfield, Mo, 1993-1997; cuid11885 (Box 89, Folder 1-5, Box 90, Folder 1-2)
  - Bulletin Pamphlet Series: Labor Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Labor News ...: Labor Work Group, Socialist Party USA, Austin, Texas, 1982; cuid11886 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Our Struggle: Latino Commission/Anti Racism Commission-DSA, Sacramento, CA, 1985; cuid11887 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Preconvention Discussion Material: League for a Revolutionary Workers Party, New York, NY, 1938; cuid11888 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - War Bulletin: League for a Revolutionary Workers Party, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid11889 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Democratic Socialism: A New Appraisal: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1953; cuid11890 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Education and the Social Order: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1989; cuid11891 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - L.I.D. Monthly: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1930-1932; cuid11892 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - L.I.D. News (League for Industrial Democracy): League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1933; cuid11893 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - LID News Bulletin: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1941-1942; cuid11894 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Looking Forward: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1966; cuid11895 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Socialism in the United States: A Brief History: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1952; cuid11896 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Resistance: League for Proletarian Revolution M-L, New York, NY, 1976-1977; cuid11897 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Resistance News: League for Proletarian Revolution M-L, New York, NY, 1985; cuid11898 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Synthesis: League for Proletarian Socialism, New York, NY, 1976; cuid11899 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Joint Internal Bulletin: League for Socialist Action/Ligue Socialiste Ouvriere and The Revolutionary Marxist Group, 1977; cuid11900 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Crises in Capitalism: League For Socialist Reconstruction, New York, NY, 1974; cuid11901 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Internationalist / Internacionalista: League for the Fourth International, New York, NY, 2003; cuid11902 (Box 129, Folder 10)